Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, UPG Senate, 1970-present UPG.RG.35
ULS Greensburg
- Committees, 1971-2016; IV.
  - Faculty Welfare Committee, 1971-2016; 12.
    11/30/77 proposed committee resolution dealing with the "involvement of all persons in an academic units...in the planning and in the implementation of academic policies and programs"
    memorandum dtd 1/31/78 from Stan Katzman to the committee dealing with "the attitude of the Oakland campus toward the regional campus on the subject of research"
    3/7/78 resolution proposed by the committee titled "Resolution on Administration Proposals in Regard to Overloads, Third Term Teaching and Basic Workloads
    9/4/87 memorandum from Herbert A. Chesler, Senate (Oakland) subject "University-wide Policy on Smoking"
    10/22/93 memorandum from L. Beeson, chair of committee, to Faculty Senate Members, subject, "Teaching Evaluation Process Review"
    1/14/08, "Student Evaluation of Teaching--Report and Survey"; Faculty Welfare Committee Report to the Senate, Mar. 12, 2008, "Student Evaluation of Teaching: Recommendations."
    Faculty Senate Minutes 9/25/12; e-mail Michael Lucci To: FD Wilson, Subj: Annual Faculty Evaluation [an Appendix C dtd 3/11/01 of an earlier document with various comments]
    Report [Feb., 2013]. "Recommendations on Revision of the Annual Faculty Evaluation Guidelines."
    [Documents, Oct. 2-3, 2013] include: Agenda for Discussion: Oct. 2 & 3, 2013 Senate Meetings, Special Senate Sub-Committee Meetings, Tenured Faculty 10/2, 10/3/2013 [meeting notes summarized by Elisa Beshero-Bondar, Faculty Senate Vice President; [notes] NTS & PF mtng, 10/2/13 [notes] NTS mtng 10/3/13.
    "Proposal for Revisions to the Policies and Procedures for Faculty Appointment, Reappointment, Promotion and Conferral of Tenure, and to the Annual Faculty Evaluation Guidelines, submitted 3/1/2014: Document, "Faculty Welfare Committee Proposal Spring 2014 [April 17, 2014]." Revisions and continued revisions of March 1, 2014 submission and subject to final aproval next academic year [2014.2014].
    2015 [Feb. 10] [Memo from UPG Senate President via UPG Senate Secretary to UPG Faculty. Copy of University of Pittsburgh (Oakland) Senate Ad Hoc Committee [document] "on NTS [Non Tenure Stream [Faculty Issues: Final Report for Presentation at Faculty [UPG Oakland] Faculty Assembly on Feb. 10, 2015".
    2015, April. Document: "Policies and Procedures for Faculty Appointment, Reappointment, Promotion, and Conferral of Tenure" (Draft Revision, April 2015; Revisions Pending Approval by Pitt-Greensburg Faculty, April 2015).
    2015, April [?] Faculty Senate: Comment Period on Policies and Procedures Document ["Policies and Procedures for Faculty Appointment, Reappointment, Promotion and Conferral of Tenure" [draft revision dtd 4/20/15, approved 44 yes, 19 no, 6 abstentions, 76% of those eligible to vote] and Preparation for Next Year. [2015, Sept. 9] "Elisa's Faculty Senate Report on the PPTP Document (2015-09-09)."
    2015, Sept. 13. [Promotion and Tenure Document: Reading and Timeline.]
    2015, Oct. 28. [Faculty Assembly election concerning the work of the Faculty Welfare Cmte.]
    2016, Feb. 1 Document: "Policies and Procedures for Faculty Appointment. Reappointment, Promotion and Conferral of Tenure." Approved by the Provost. Feb. 1, 2016.
    2016, Feb. 9. From: LJ Kirsch, Vice Provost for Faculty Aff., Dev., & Diversity. To: EB-B. [Approval letter for Promotion and Tenure Guidelines document.]
    - Faculty Welfare Committee, 1971-2016 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 2)
  - Faculty Workload Committee, 2014; 13.
    [n.b.: This committee was not established by the UPG Senate but by the UPG Administration as an ad hoc committee in re "Compensation Plan for Supervision of Capstones, Independent Studies, and Internships." [Plan report approved by Dr. Wesley Jamison, VPAA and Faculty Workload Committee, Feb. 12, 2014. [Included as document of discussion at Senate meetings of 3/27 and 3/31/14.]
    - Faculty Workload Committee, 2014 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 2)
  - Facilities and Supplies Committee, 1971-1993; 14.
    Files, 1971, 1973-75, 1978, 1980, 1993
    Consist principally of minutes of the Faculty Senate meetings which have oral reports by the committee or items of interest to the committee; also include: a 1974 "Report on Questionnaire Distributed by the Facilities and Supplies Committee"; memorandum dtd 4 Dec. 1975 in re "Centralization of Audio Visual Equipment"; Dec. 1, 1978 "Committee's recommendation regarding the "motion concerning a change in the grading policy of UPG", a joint report from the Academic Standards Committee and Facilities and Supplies Committee.
    - Facilities and Supplies Committee, 1971-1993 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 2)
  - Grant-in-Aid Committee [Summer Grant-in-Aid Committee; Faculty Summer Grant Committee], 1972-1979; 15.
    Files, 1972-79.
    Contain: minutes of the Faculty Senate meetings which contain oral reports by the committee or items of interest to the committee; proposal to establish Grant-in-Aid committee (1972); guidelines; procedures; applications/proposals; awards; written reports by awardees. 1973 was the first year in which awards were granted. Awards: 1973, Guy Rossetti, Mike Rubinoff, Kamile Rustam, Joanne Viano; 1974, Frank McGlynn, Larry Whatule, Ken Bell, Ruth Kuschmierz; 1975, Janet Van Zoeren, Tom Leschine, Nancy Washington, Mary Grace O'Donnell; 1976, Dan Milberg, William Kadunce, Colette Levin, Stan Katzman; 1977, Guy Rossetti, Manhar Vyas, Stan Katzman, Tom Wolf, Norman McWhinney, Joanne Viano, Frank McGlynn, Ted Zaleskiweicz; 1978, Collette Levin, Diane Marsh, Nancy Washington, Frank McGlynn, Larry Whatule, Judith Zimmerman, Tom Wolf; 1979, Judith Zimmerman, Mike Rubinoff, Eleanor Silvis, Lillian Beeson, Frank McGlynn.
    - Grant-in-Aid Committee [Summer Grant-in-Aid Committee; Faculty Summer Grant Committee], 1972-1979 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Instructional Technology Committee, 2009-2016; 16.
    File contains: "Faculty Senate Instructional Technology Committee recommendations to University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Faculty Senate, 10 April 2009."
    2016, Mar.-Apr. Document: "Survey of faculty use of technology, Mar-Apr 2016: Results." 35 p.
    - Instructional Technology Committee, 2009-2016 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Library Committee, 1971-2001; 17.
    Files, 1971-80, 1987-88, 1997, 2001.
    Contain for the most part minutes of the Faculty Senate meetings which have oral reports from the committee or items of interest to the committee; also include: "Progress Report on the Activities of the Library Committee" dtd 4/15/75; agenda 10/31/75 meeting; committee report dtd 11/25/75; committee report 1997. See also RG35 Library, Series: Library Committee--General Files.
    - Library Committee, 1971-2001 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Local Advisory Board Representative, Ad Hoc Committee on the Selection of a, 1973-1974; 18.
    Files, 1973-74.
    2 items: memorandum of September 25, 1973 reconfirming the selection of Dr. Kenneth Bell and Dr. Donald Reilly to serve another term (1973-75) on the Advisory Board of UPG; 11/20/74 minutes of the Faculty Council containing the report of the committee.
    - Local Advisory Board Representative, Ad Hoc Committee on the Selection of a, 1973-1974 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Nominating Committee, 1971-1980; 19.
    Files, 1971-74, 1976-78, 1980.
    Consist of minutes of Faculty Senate meetings which contain nominations of candidates and discussion of items in re nominations and elections.
    - Nominating Committee, 1971-1980 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1992; 20.
    Files, 1992.
    1 item: call to meeting 12/1/92.
    - Planning and Budgeting Committee, 1992 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Professional Development, Ad Hoc Committee for, 1989; 21.
    Files, 1989.
    Consist of memoranda in re formation of the committee, a list of those interested in serving on the committee; undtd and untitled document [Report?, Memorandum?] prepared by the Ad Cmte.
    - Professional Development, Ad Hoc Committee for, 1989 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Salary Benchmarking Task Force Report, Pitt-Greensburg, 2005-2006; 22.
    Contains: [Report] 2005 Submitted to the Pitt-Greensburg Faculty Senate; Faculty Salary Benchmarking [Report], UPJ Faculty Senate Ad Hoc Committee on Salary Benchmarking, April 19, 2006.
    - Salary Benchmarking Task Force Report, Pitt-Greensburg, 2005-2006 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Staff Welfare Committee, 1973-1993; 23.
    Files, 1973-74, 1993.
    Contain: minutes of the Faculty Senate meetings which have oral reports by the committee or discussion of items to the committee; 1/8/93 memorandum in re request for clarification for handling "snow days".
    - Staff Welfare Committee, 1973-1993 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Tenure, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1973-1974; 24.
    Contain: memorandum dtd 9/17/73 from Donald T. Reilly, Chairman, Faculty Welfare Committee, subject, "Proposal for Formation of an Ad Hoc Tenure Committee"; minutes of Faculty Senate meetings which contain oral reports by the committee or items of interest to the committee; undtd memorandum [Oct., 1973?] giving names of members of committee.
    - Tenure, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1973-1974 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - Undergraduate Programs, Provost's Advisory Committee on, 1972-1981; 25.
    Files, 1972-1981.
    Contain: minutes of UPG Faculty Senate meetings which contain oral reports by the UPG representative to the committee or items of interest on the committee; agendas, reports, documents for PACUP meetings; Document, "Report for the Task Force on Evaluation of Academic and Administrative Programs", Univ. of Pgh., University Senate, Final Draft, [1977?]; Report, "Revised University Council on Interdisciplinary Programs", [1978]; Proposal, "Restructuring Undergraduate Education", [1978]; Document, "Planning Directions for Academic Programs 1980-1990", [1978]; Proposal, "Legal Studies Major", [1978]; Proposal, "Paralegal Certificate", [1978]; Proposal, "Media Communication Concentration", [1978]; Proposal "Administration Area Concentration", [1978]; Proposal, "Architectural Studies Program," [1978]; Proposal, "Major in Religious Studies', [1978]; Proposal, "Major in Biochemistry and Biophysics", [1978]; Proposal, "Undergraduate Major in Applied Mathematics", [1978]; proposal for an undergraduate dual major in Business and CAS, [1978]; proposal for an undergraduate major in Statistics, [1978]; "Report on Academic Change on the Regional Campuses', [1978]; "Preliminary Planning Proposals for a Business/Accounting Major in the School of General Studies", [1980]; Proposal, "New Undergraduate Major in Microbiology", [1980].
    - Undergraduate Programs, Provost's Advisory Committee on, 1972-1981 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - University Facilities and Infrastructure of the Pitt Greensburg Faculty Senate, Committee On, 2015; 26.
    Report on Meeting 10-05-2015.
    - University Facilities and Infrastructure of the Pitt Greensburg Faculty Senate, Committee On, 2015 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
  - University Relations, Committee on, 1998; 27.
    Files, 1998.
    - University Relations, Committee on, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 3)
- Representatives to the Faculty Senate, 1972-1995; V.
  - Staff Representatives to Faculty Senate, 1972-1995; 1.
    Files, 1972-73, 1977, 1994-95.
    Deal primarily with elections of staff representatives to the Faculty Senate.
    - Staff Representatives to Faculty Senate, 1972-1995 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Student Government Association Representatives to Faculty Senate, 1972-1980; 2.
    Files, 1972-1980.
    Contain: various minutes of the Faculty Senate which contain oral reports by SGA representatives or of interest to them; lists of SGA officers.
    - Student Government Association Representatives to Faculty Senate, 1972-1980 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
- Secretary, 1972-2016; VI.
  Files, 1972-2016
  Contain for the most part information on various elections
  also include: "Advice To The Senate Secretary": a report month-by-month calendar of what to do when prepared by Sayre N. Greenfield, May 1997
  memorandum 12/9/77, Carl F. Poke, subject, "Hiring for School Year 77-78 of New Faculty"
  memorandum 10/5/78, Carl F. Poke, subject, "Hiring of New Faculty for School Year 1978/79"
  memorandum 10/15/88, Carl F. Poke, subject. "Full-Time Faculty Hiring for School Year 1988-89--Affirmative Action Report"
  memorandum 10/27/88, Larry J. Whatule, Director of Admissions, subject, "Report on Minority Recruitment"
  memorandum 11/11/88, Dr. Guy Rossetti, subject, "Staff [non-faculty] Report, 1988"
  copies of resolutions, subjects: rescheduling of final examinations [1974]
  bringing the UPG Academic Calendar in conformity with the Pitt Oakland Academic Calendar with regard to the ADD/DROP period [1988]
  implementation of recommendations developed for the Middle States Association [1983]
  the continuing of a faculty member's service to the university; minority imbalance among staff, faculty and the student body.
  2016, April 8. LAS to ALF et al. Subject: Updated UPG Senate Membership List 2015-2016.
  2016, April 11. LAS to Colleagues. Subject: 2016 faculty workshop schedule (May 9, 10).
  2016, April 25. From ALF to LAS. Subject: Spring 2016 Faculty Senate Final Election Results.
  - Secretary, 1972-2016 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
- Subject Files, 1971-2006; VII.
  NOTE: The subject files, for the most part, consist of copies of minutes of the UPG Senate which have references to a particular subject. When a particular subject file contains material other than such minutes, a descriptive note appears. The subject files have not been consistently maintained and may be incomplete of all references made to the subject in other minutes of the UPG Senate. [faz]
  - AAUP (Greensburg Chapter), 1971; 1.
    - AAUP (Greensburg Chapter), 1971 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Academic Cabinet, 1972; 2.
    - Academic Cabinet, 1972 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Academic Development, 1972; 3.
    Contains copy of memorandum dtd 7/5/72 from Dr. Albert B. Smith to Dr. Robert J. Nossen, Assoc. Provost for Regional Campuses, subject, "Possible Directions for the Academic Development of the Greensburg Campus".
    - Academic Development, 1972 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Academic Integrity, Proposed Guidelines [Students, Faculty], 3/9/1982; 4.
    - Academic Integrity, Proposed Guidelines [Students, Faculty], 3/9/1982 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Academic Integrity—Students, 2005-2006; 5.
    - Academic Integrity—Students, 2005-2006 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Academic Programs, 1972-1981; 6.
    Contains: copy of ABS memorandum of 7/5/72 to Albert J. Nossen; memorandum dtd 1/12/78 from Dr. Albert B. Smith to Vice Chancellor Jack E. Freeman, Chairman, University Planning Advisory Council, subject, "Planning Directions for Academic Programs, 1980-1990", UPG Reactions"; document dtd 11/3/80 titled "University Policies Relating to Reorganization or Termination of Academic Programs" together with draft of document dtd 7/11/80 and also contains a copy of 1981 edition of the document. Academic Review (1976) Contains copy of "Academic Review Resolution (as amended) Approved by Senate on Feb. 19, 1976.
    - Academic Programs, 1972-1981 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Add/Drop, 1978; 7.
    - Add/Drop, 1978 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Administrative Salary Expenditures, 1974; 8.
    Reference in minutes of UPG Senate 3/29/74. File does not have a copy of the report on Administrative Salary Expenditures which is mentioned in the last sentence of the first paragraph in I of the UPG Senate minutes of 3/29/74.
    - Administrative Salary Expenditures, 1974 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Admissions, Enrollment, 1971-1980, 1988; 9.
    - Admissions, Enrollment, 1971-1980, 1988 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Advising, 1973-1974; 10.
    Senate meeting minutes 3/8/73 contain recommendation of the Academic Standards Committee in re scheduling, advising and course selection procedure.
    - Advising, 1973-1974 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Advisory Board, UPG, 1978; 11.
    Contains an undtd (1980's?) list of Advisory Board members.
    Appeals Procedure, University Wide Faculty (1978)
    Contains draft of document in re "Faculty Appeals, Principles and Procedures" dtd 2/16/78.
    - Advisory Board, UPG, 1978 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Appointment, Promotion, Tenure, 1970-2003; 12.
    Contains: memorandum dtd 19 June 1970 from Nancy van Vuuren, Chairman, Regional Campuses Faculty Senate Council to Dr. Richard Rose, Assistant Provost for the Regional Campuses, subject, "Faculty Comment on the Ranking Procedures proposals made in response to the memorandum of 15 May 1970 from Dr. Rose..." with attachment of a memorandum from NvV in re "Finalization of the By-Laws for the RCFS (Regional Campus Faculty Senate)"; p. 2 of a ltr dtd 11/10/70 from Dr. Jerome L. Rosenberg, Dean, Faculty of Arts and Sciences to NvV in re criteria for faculty advancement in Oakland; memorandum dtd 2/11/71 from C.F. Poke, Dean of Instruction to All Full-Time Faculty [UPG], subject, "Criteria for Appointment and Promotion"; document [1974]. "Senate Educational Policies Committee Evaluation of Tenure Commission Report"; memorandum 3/21/78 from Joanne J. Viano to members of the UPG Senate, subject, "Statement of Tenure" [at the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg]; draft document 4/7/78, memorandum, documents from the Ad Hoc Committee to Review UPG Policies and Procedures Pertaining to Appointment, Reappointment, Promotion and the Conferral of Tenure; Proposed Revisions o Tenure and Promotion Documents, 1/6/03.
    See also: Ser.: Committees. Faculty Welfare Committee.
    - Appointment, Promotion, Tenure, 1970-2003 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Audio Visual Matters, 1973-1981; 13.
    - Audio Visual Matters, 1973-1981 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 4)
  - Basketball, 1973-1975; 14.
    Contains: an undtd (1973?) paper which gives reasons for bringing basketball back to UPG, budgetary considerations, estimated 1973-74 budget-basketball program, and a proposed 1974-75 budget-basketball program.
    - Basketball, 1973-1975 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Benefits, 1975-1976; 15.
    Contains: copy of the resolution on "Benefits" amended and passed by the UPG Senate on 4/2/76.
    - Benefits, 1975-1976 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Capital Campaign, 1988-1989; 16.
    Contains a draft letter to faculty in re support for the Building of the Future Capital Campaign.
    - Capital Campaign, 1988-1989 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Class Cancellation, 1978; 17.
    Contains a copy of a resolution dealing with the cancellation of classes due to inclement weather.
    - Class Cancellation, 1978 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Classroom Visitation, 10/02/2000; 18.
    - Classroom Visitation, 10/02/2000 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Continuing Education, 1979-1980; 19.
    - Continuing Education, 1979-1980 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Courses, Re-entry, 1979; 20.
    - Courses, Re-entry, 1979 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Cross-registration, 1973; 21.
    - Cross-registration, 1973 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Deborah Smith Memorial Fund, 1972; 22.
    - Deborah Smith Memorial Fund, 1972 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Dormitories, Housing, 1975-1978; 23.
    - Dormitories, Housing, 1975-1978 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - English Composition, 1971-1977; 24.
    Contains: a memorandum from Donald T. Reilly to the Academic Standards Committee transmitting a report entitled, "A Report to the Academic Standards Committee on Student Writing"; a memorandum from D.T. Reilly to Members of the UPG Senate, subject, "Proposal on Student Writing".
    - English Composition, 1971-1977 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Evaluation, Teaching, 1978; 25.
    Contains: text of resolutions concerning Student Evaluation of Teaching.
    - Evaluation, Teaching, 1978 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Financial Aid, 1979; 26.
    - Financial Aid, 1979 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Fine System, UPG Library, 1979; 27.
    - Fine System, UPG Library, 1979 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Foreign Languages, 1975; 28.
    Contains a copy of the Dartmouth Intensive Language Model [c. 1975].
    - Foreign Languages, 1975 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1979; 29.
    - Freshman Orientation, 1979 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Gifts, 1980; 30.
    - Gifts, 1980 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Grade Inflation, 1972-1976; 31.
    Contains copy of [1976?] Interim Report, Academic Standards Committee.
    - Grade Inflation, 1972-1976 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Grading Policy, 1974-1982; 32.
    Contains: copy of University of Pittsburgh FAS Gazette, Nov. 15, 1976 which has "Statement on the Grading Policies" prepared by E.T. Newman, "Grade Inflation" in Context: an Attempt at Clarification" by Philip K. Wion and a "Questionnaire on Grading"; copy of FAS Gazette 6/15/77 which deals, in part, with "Numerical Equivalents of Plus and Minus Grading" and the "Honors Program"; "motion concerning a change in the grading policy at UPG" [10/6/78]; report by the Academic Standards Committee and Facilities and Supplies Committee dtd 12/1/78, subject, "Committees' recommendation regarding the "motion concerning a change in the grading policy at UPG""; memorandum dtd 1/14/82 from Joanne J. Viano to All Faculty, Subj.: "Grades and Grading Policy".
    - Grading Policy, 1974-1982 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Higher Education Guidelines, 1972; 33.
    Contains copy of "Higher Education Guidelines Executive Order 11246 ["Nondiscrimination Under Federal Contracts"]. Document issued by U.S. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare, Office of the Secretary, Office for Civil Rights.
    - Higher Education Guidelines, 1972 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Institutional Review Board, Univ. of Pittsburgh, 08/29/2005; 34.
    - Institutional Review Board, Univ. of Pittsburgh, 08/29/2005 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Interdisciplinary A.B., 1974; 35.
    - Interdisciplinary A.B., 1974 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Kenneth E. Bell Memorial Fund, 1974-1976; 36.
    Subjects: Kenneth E. Bell Memorial Fund; Nature Preserve; Kenneth E. Bell Trail.
    - Kenneth E. Bell Memorial Fund, 1974-1976 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Middle States Evaluation, 1970-1983; 37.
    (1970, 1980, [1983?])
    - Middle States Evaluation, 1970-1983 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Mission and Goals, 1974; 38.
    Document, "Statement of Mission and Goals of the University of Pittsburgh", Office of Planning and Budget, University of Pittsburgh, 1974.
    - Mission and Goals, 1974 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Nursing Program (UPG), 1972; 39.
    - Nursing Program (UPG), 1972 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Pennsylvania Post Secondary Planning Committee, 1974; 40.
    - Pennsylvania Post Secondary Planning Committee, 1974 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Pharmacy, School of, 1976; 41.
    Discussion of School of Pharmacy Proposal at UPG.
    - Pharmacy, School of, 1976 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)
  - Planning and Resource Management System (PRMS), 1980; 42.
    Document, "The Planning and Resource Management System University of Pittsburgh", November, 1980. 23 p.
    - Planning and Resource Management System (PRMS), 1980 (Museum-cabinet 1, Shelf 8, Box 5)